veoh.com 2019-11-08

# Privacy Policy

Veoh is committed to protecting your privacy when you use Veoh, which is comprised of the Veoh website, currently located at www.veoh.com and the Veoh client, a downloadable application that enables users to view content. This Privacy Policy informs you of the types of information we collect about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom we disclose it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information. 

It is very important that you read and understand our Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms set out in our Privacy Policy, please do not use Veoh.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any revisions will be effective upon posting the new Privacy Policy on the Veoh website at <https://www.veoh.com/corporate/privacypolicy>. We will advise you that changes have been made by posting a notice on our website or otherwise. Your visit to or use of Veoh constitutes your acceptance of the terms of our Privacy Policy. You are advised to consult our Privacy Policy regularly for any changes (revisions will be reflected by the "last update" notation below).

**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding Veoh's policies or practices relating to privacy, please direct them to [privacy@veoh.com](mailto:privacy@veoh.com).

**

This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 7, 2008.

## Collection of Information

While using Veoh you may gather information on our website, view, publish and download video or other content, share, comment on or post information, subscribe to one of our services, join groups, or participate in other activities available throughout Veoh. In doing so, we may collect certain information about you. 

We may automatically collect certain aggregated data regarding your use of Veoh, like the number of users and frequency and manner of usage of Veoh. We may also collect aggregated information regarding the use of our subscription-based services, such as the extent to which certain features are used. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of our user base, sales, customer patterns and related site information. In addition, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected by Veoh and our third-party advertising providers (such as, for example, DoubleClick and other providers ) during your use of Veoh and in serving advertisements to our website, including, for example, the number of times you have viewed an advertisement (but not your name, address, or other personal information).

We may also use cookies to track and understand the traffic on our website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that our website places onto your computer's hard drive. Cookies identify your computer hard drive so that we can recognize you the next time you visit us. We use cookies to collect and store some information about you, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access our website and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website.

Third party advertisements displayed on or in connection with the Veoh website may also contain cookies set by such advertisers. We do not control these cookies and users of Veoh should check the privacy policy of such advertisers to understand whether and how it uses cookies.

We may collect and/or you may choose to post profile information about your interests, groups or affiliations, your videos, photos, personal statements, or other information about yourself.

We may collect and/ or you may choose to post personally identifiable information when you seek access to certain portions of Veoh, when you view, publish or download content, and/or register for or participate in our services. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, physical and e-mail addresses, phone and/or fax numbers, Internet address, software and hardware attributes, type of computer and credit card or other payment information. Please be aware that if you disclose personally identifiable information in your profile or when you post comments or publish videos, the information may become publicly available.

## Use of Information

Aggregated information that we collect is used to better understand how Veoh is used, and to improve the online experience of our users. This information is not used in a way that will personally identify you. Aggregated information, as well as other non-personal information is also used by Veoh and our advertising providers to facilitate and monitor the serving of advertisements. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to opt out, please go to <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/>. In addition, the cookies that are used by Veoh and its advertisers are used to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. In the same manner, we may also engage other third parties to monitor the usage of, and serve advertising to Veoh. These third parties may use cookies and web beacons (which collect non-personally identifiable information regarding user behavior on our website) to collect such information, which is also used to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. You may disable cookies by following directions on your web browser. Disabling cookies also disables web beacons. You should be aware, however, that by disabling cookies you may be unable to access certain services and features of Veoh. 

We may also use information about you and your activities on our website to customize your experience and to customize the content or features of Veoh and for the purpose of tailoring the online advertising you may encounter. 

You may elect to hide your site activity or profile information so that it will not be seen by other users.

We may use your personally identifiable information to fulfill your requests for services, to communicate with you about your account, to support your online activities, and to respond to your questions. We may use your personally identifiable information to notify you of changes to Veoh, the Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy. We may also use your personally identifiable information and/or your profile information to personalize your interactive experience on Veoh. For example, if you have given us permission, we may use your information to inform you of other Veoh and/or third-party products or services you may find valuable. We may also use the information you provide to make improvements that better serve our users' needs. 

To edit your personal information that you entered when you created your account or make changes to your profile information, you must log-in to Veoh.com and click your username at the top of any page to manage your account and adjust your settings. You may also choose to hide certain information to limit its availability. If you prefer not to receive information about additional products and services, you can choose not to receive this information by opting-out. 

## Disclosure of Information

We may share aggregated statistical information and profile information about users of Veoh with third-parties, including our distributors, vendors, advertisers actual and potential customers, business partners and third-parties that offer products or services for use with Veoh. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Veoh will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-parties, with the following exceptions:

  1. Your name or screen name may be available through search indexes.
  2. As necessary to third parties who perform services for us in operating and marketing Veoh, included but not limited to the monitoring of user behavior on our website and the processing of payments for products or services. 
  3. If you obtain the Veoh client bundled with product(s) from a third-party company, we may share some of your personally identifiable information (but not your credit card information) with that company. If we share your personally identifiable information with such a company, that company's privacy policy will govern its use of your information. 
  4. We may be obliged or deem it necessary or appropriate to disclose your information in certain special situations. These situations include: in response to legal process such as a court order or subpoena; to prevent or combat fraud; as required by federal or state law; enforcement of our Terms of Use; and protection of the rights, property or safety of Veoh, our users or others. 
  5. We may disclose your information in connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of our company and to parents, subsidiaries or affiliates of Veoh. If you access any third-party applications, follow links from the Veoh website to another website, or view Veoh from another website, the information you disclose may no longer be covered by this Privacy Policy. You are encouraged to check whether other privacy policies will govern before you release any personal information. 

## Security

Veoh is committed to taking appropriate measures to protect your privacy against unauthorized disclosures. Veoh uses a variety of secure techniques designed to protect your information. 

While we have implemented safeguards, you should be aware that Internet security technology rapidly changes. As such, we cannot guarantee that the safeguards we employ today can protect your personal information from the threats of tomorrow, or that our security measures are failsafe and not subject to circumvention or unauthorized intrusion. You should also be aware that, despite our best efforts, factors beyond our control may result in disclosure of data. 

## Young Children

We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. To best protect your child's privacy, we suggest that you carefully supervise your child's access to the Internet and our website. For more information on how to protect your child's privacy, you can visit the Federal Trade Commission's Kidzprivacy page, accessible via [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

## Opt-Out

Veoh provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us regarding products and services in which you may be interested. If you do not opt-out at the time you provide information, but choose to opt-out later, send an email to optout@veoh.com or click [here](mailto:optout@veoh.com) to send an email indicating that you no longer wish to receive such communications. Please provide your name and physical and/or email address(es) at which you are receiving the unwanted communications. We reserve the right to send you administrative message, service announcements, and other similar communications without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

## Notice for Users Outside of the United States

You should be aware that the United States and other countries have not harmonized their privacy regulations. Because Veoh is intended specifically for users in the United States, we have written our Privacy Policy to satisfy United States regulations and make no representations regarding the laws and regulations of other jurisdictions. By using Veoh, you agree to the level of privacy protection set out in our Privacy Policy. 

FC2  
4730 South Fort Apache Road  
Suite 300  
Las Vegas, NV 89147  
Tel: (310) 409-8217  
Fax: (310) 496-2823  
Email: [info@veoh.com](mailto:info@veoh.com)
